[{"answer": "Thanks. You know this could sound crazy but, what do you think about adding a drawer for", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Blanket", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "That thick", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Like that", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Maybe like this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Yeah, like that", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yeah, like that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "That is what I want.", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Its been a long night. You go home and get some sleep", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "That's what I want", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What is that smell", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "You're swimming in the that place? The most heavily trafficked overly contaminated waterway on the eastern seaboard", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "That's that place", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Technically that place has more gross tonnage", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Why don't you just have him paged", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "A bomb threat? Why would I call in a bomb threat", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Can't you think of something. Call in a bomb threat", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Just CALL", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Hey you kids know tune", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "A bomb in the building, oh, m'god. Quick, everyone under the desk.", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "It is obtrusive, isn't it", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "FINE? WHAT SIZE", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "SEVEN AND FIVE EIGHTHS!", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I am totally loving it. Uh, you know ... we should um ... get going", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What smell", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hello are you the bomber", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "my friend here is busting his ass on those hats", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Oh, hey", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "my friend, .. uh my friend", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Just lie down", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "All right. I'll be right there., my friend I gotta go", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Hey, watch where you're kicking", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my frien", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "I can't believe it. Hey, I'll meet you at the coffee shop", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Nap.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah.", "qsentId": 36}]